Finding Aid for the Thomas S. Jones/John R. Jones Family Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Thomas S. Jones/John R. Jones Family Papers
1848-1859
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0231
.03 linear feet
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the accounting records of a plantation in Charleston, Mississippi; the correspondence of two brothers, Thomas S. Jones [who was in charge of the plantation] and John R. Jones [who was practicing medicine in Marshall County, Tennessee]; and speech. Buleah Davis donated this collection in 1939.
- Accounting Records
  - Account Sale of Cotton and Final Settlement, 1851 – 1852
  - Invoice of Sundries, 1852
- Correspondence
  - T. S. Jones to J. R. Jones, July 23, 1848
  - T. S. Jones to J. R. Jones, December 17, 1849
  - T. S. Jones to J. R. Jones, August 1, 1850
  - T. S. Jones to J. R. Jones, June 21, 1852
  - T. S. Jones to J. R. Jones, August 20, 1852
  - C. W. Robertson to John R. Jones, April 2, 1855
- Speech
  - J. L. M. Curry of Alabama
  - On the Election of Speaker and the Progress of Anti-Slaveryism
  - Delivered in the House of Representatives
  - December 10, 1859